<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aniket Bhatnagar</title>
    <link>https://www.aniketbhatnagar.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aniket Bhatnagar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.aniketbhatnagar.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My tech skills</title>
      <link>https://www.aniketbhatnagar.com/key-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.aniketbhatnagar.com/key-skills/</guid>
      <description>Key skills As I believe in using the right tool for the job, I am not married to any technology and language in particular. Below is the list of skills I have acquired over the years working in the tech industry:&#xA;Languages: Java, Scala, Python, Typescript, Go Databases: MySQL, Postgres, MongoDB, DynamoDB, HBase, Redis Tools/Frameworks: JEE, Spring, Play! Framework 2, Spark, Hadoop, Kafka, SQS, Kinesis, Cadence, Temporal Cloud: AWS (EC2, ASG, ALB/ELB, RDS, SQS, SNS, Lambda, API Gateway, Route 53, Kinesis, CloudFront, etc) Blockchain: Ethereum, Bitcoin, multi-cryptocurrency wallet infrastructure, smart contract based sweeps Interests: Payments, Highly scalable architectures, blockchain/distributed consensus, distributed systems, eventual consistency, non-blocking I/O, real time streaming, improving/replatforming legacy systems iteratively, atleast once message processing, performance tuning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SapientNitro&#39;s game changer</title>
      <link>https://www.aniketbhatnagar.com/game-changer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.aniketbhatnagar.com/game-changer/</guid>
      <description>Recognition Watch During the early stages of my career, after wining various awards like rookie of the year award in 2008 for best trainee, I was later recognized as SapientNitro’s (now Publicis Sapient) Game Changer in 2014 for my outstanding contributions. Watch my story here: Your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos, but don&#39;t worry, you can download it and watch it with your favorite video player! Read Full write up here .</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
